hey guys what's going on with this thing
right here how are we going to evaluate
this this is pretty confusing this thing
is quite ambiguous as far as I can tell
there's two ways to interpret this we
have this fraction on top divided by
this on bottom or we have the 4830
divided by all of this on bottom I don't
think it's clear which one of these is
intended so let's solve both of them and
see what happens I think I have a pretty
good idea and if you want to try it on
your own pause it right now cuz I'm
going to solve it in 3 2 1 let's do this
one first on bottom here the square root
of this fraction is equal to the
fraction of the square roots and then we
can put the two on top now we have two
fractions another way to think of this
is this fraction divided by this
fraction and we can express it like this
and now anytime you're dividing
fractions a cool way to handle this is
leave the first fraction alone change
the Divide to a multiply and flip the
second fraction on this side right here
we can break down the 805 into 23 * 35
and the square root of this product is
equal to the product of these square
roots and now we can smush it all
together the < TK of 23 on top and
bottom can cancel each other out and
then we can shift things around > 35 * >
35 is 35 and 35 * 2 is 70 4830 / 70 is
69 nice and that's the answer to our
first one so once again we have this
divided by this let's rewrite it like
this and then we can put the 4830 over
one and then we'll copy this down switch
the Divide to a multiply and flip the
second fraction once again the square
root of this fraction is equal to the
fraction of the square roots and then we
can put the two on top and now we have
another fraction divided by a fraction
let's express it like this and then once
again we can copy down this stuff change
the Divide to a multiply and flip the
divided by fraction we can smush
everything together and let's change
this 805 into a 23 * 35 and the < TK of
23 * 35 is the same thing as the < of 23
* < TK of 35 from here these two ones
ain't doing nothing so they can go away
and then rooot 35 overun 35 those can
also go away and then < tk23 * < tk23 is
equal to the whole number 23 and on top
4830 * 2 is equal to
960 and then 960 / 23 is equal to 420
and that's the answer to our second
ambiguous case so in conclusion this is
ambiguous we don't know what it is equal
to but we do know that it's equal to
either 69 nice or 420 how exciting